stake.com 2004-04-11

# @stake Privacy Policy

_Last Updated: December 1, 2003_

@stake, Inc. is committed to protecting the privacy of visitors to this website. This Privacy Policy explains the company's website visitor data collection and use practices. This site is designed to provide potential clients, partners, employees, and the public at large with information about the company, as well as its services, products, research and tools. In addition, visitors can download and purchase security tools and software.

Visitors to the site may be asked to provide personal information in order to make a request, download a product, or obtain certain information. The type of information required will vary according to the request. By submitting data, visitors to the website agree to @stake's use of such information as described in this Privacy Policy.

## How will @stake Use my Information?

Unless otherwise indicated at the time of data submission, visitor information will be used only for the specific purpose for which it is provided; for example, to respond to an information request, to add a visitor to a distribution list, to review a resume etc. Secondary uses of information are limited to monitoring business development opportunities related to site usage.

@stake may keep a visitor's personally-identifiable information on file and use it to contact the visitor for feedback on @stake website content, products, and services, as well as to provide the visitor with timely notices of product releases and service developments that address the visitors needs and requirements. Visitors who download or purchase software products from the @stake website may be contacted regarding current and future versions of the software. All @stake-initiated customer notices will contain opt-out elections. In addition, if visitors do not wish to be contacted, they may send an email at any time to [privacy@atstake.com](mailto:privacy@atstake.com?subject=remove) with "remove" as the subject line and full name and email information in the body of the message.

## Does @stake use Cookies?

@stake uses cookies to estimate and report our total audience size and traffic and to conduct research to improve @stake's content, advertisements, products, and services.

## Will @stake Provide my Information to Other Parties?

@stake does not sell, rent, loan or lease any personal information collected on this site, however such information may be transferred in connection with a sale or other transfer of @stake, Inc. or one of its subsidiaries. During the fulfillment of visitor requests, @stake may rely on trusted third-party companies (e.g. purchasing our products). While @stake only uses reputable companies, @stake makes no claims or warranties regarding their business practices. Visitors are encouraged to visit the third-party sites via links provided on this site if they have questions regarding their privacy policies.

@stake will disclose a visitor's personal information if it is required to do so by law or if such action is necessary to comply with legal process served on @stake, or to protect the safety of visitors or the public from an immediate and material threat that cannot reasonably be addressed without such disclosure.

@stake may provide links to third-party websites as a service to visitors. @stake cannot control and is not responsible for the privacy and/or information collection practices of such third-party websites, which may differ from those of this site. @stake encourages visitors to review and understand the privacy policies on these websites before providing any information.

## Where will my Information be Used?

Visitor information may be processed in the U.S, or any other country in which @stake or its subsidiaries has a separate office, and by using this site, visitors consent to any transfers of personally identifiable information outside the U.S. @stake abides by the safe harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union.

## How Can I Modify Information I May Have Provided to @stake?

Visitors may correct, update, and/or delete any personally identifiable information they have submitted to the site by sending an e-mail to [privacy@atstake.com](mailto:privacy@atstake.com?subject=change%20information), with "change information" as the subject line and full name and revised information in the body.

## Notice Regarding Children

This website does not publish content that is targeted to children. The website is not intended, or directed at, children 13 years of age or younger, and @stake will not knowingly or intentionally collect or maintain information about anyone under the age of 13.

## Changes to this Statement

@stake may occasionally update this Privacy Policy. When this occurs, @stake will revise the "last updated" date on this Privacy Policy to reflect the new date. For changes that @stake believes to be significant and material, @stake will notify visitors by placing a prominent notice on this website.

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, please e-mail us at [privacy@atstake.com](mailto:privacy@atstake.com).

» Back to the Previous Page
